（忆往昔）
我是克劳力
The name's Crowley.
你就是克劳力
You're Crowley?
看来你听说过我了
I see you have heard of me.
我能实现你的任何愿望 同志
I can give you anything you want, mate.
- 而我只要 - 我的灵魂
- All I need is… - My soul.
你出卖了自己的灵魂
You sold your soul?
噢 典当更贴切些
Oh, more like pawned it.
- 我完全乐意将它归还 - 好啊 那马上还来
- I fully intend to give it back. - Well, then give it back!
- 不行 - 是不行还是不愿意
- I can't. - Can't or won't?
我不愿意 行了吗 那是我的保险
I won't, all right? It's insurance.
- 鲁弗斯·特纳 猎魔人 - 是你的老友吗
- Rufus Turner. He's a hunter. - One of your old friends?
朋友 他可绝不是友善之人
Friend? He's not the christmas-card type.
先生们 我是乔迪·米尔斯警长
Gentlemen. I'm sheriff Jody Mills.
相信我们之前没见过
I don't believe we've had the pleasure.
我是威利斯探员
Agent Willis speaking.
- 鲍比吗 - 老天
- Bobby? - Oh…
这么说你认识鲍比·辛格
So you know Bobby Singer?
鲍比 警长不是很讨厌你么
Bobby, I thought the sheriff hated you?
直到五天前她确实很恨我
She did till five days ago.
五天前发生了什么
What happened five days ago?
整个镇上开始出现丧尸
The dead started rising all over town.
鲍比 你就打算坐那儿吗
Bobby, you just gonna sit there?
不 我正准备跳大河之舞
No, I'm gonna riverdance.
还真是太妄费十字路口的交易了
Really wasted that crossroads deal.
天杀的
Son of a bitch.
嘿 拜托 我可是十字路口之王
Hello … king of the crossroads.
你没事儿吧
Are you okay?
当然 我好得很
yeah, I'm great.
因为有那么几次 你让我觉得很纳闷
'cause there's been a few times that you got me wondering.
- 总觉得你有点儿不一样了 - 我很好
- Something's different with you. - I'm okay.
你可是去过地狱的 萨姆
You went to hell, Sam.
昨天 加尔维斯顿海岸受到十英尺高的海浪
Yesterday, this Galveston shoreline was being pounded.
（加尔维斯顿 得克萨斯州）
和风速达每小时150米的飓风袭击
by 10-foot swells and winds up to 150 miles per hour.
（一年前）
然而今天却是万里无云
But today, well, there's not a cloud in sight.
蒂芬尼飓风登陆海湾之后就结束了
Hurricane Tiffany has broken up over the gulf,
根据我们的5日短期预报
and our 5-day forecast calls for nothing…
接下来几天都将风和日丽
…but sun and clear skies.
看来上帝很中意我们
I guess somebody up there likes us.
[咒语]
我们一直都玩得很开心哈
Been making merry, have we?
死吧你
Bite me.
没想到你还好那口
If that's your thing.
萨姆那华丽的一跳真是太完美了
That swan dive of Sam's was a thing of beauty.
表现绝佳 世人赞扬
Tens all the way 'round,
让路同学白忙了一场
standing "O" from the romanian judge.
你应该引以为傲的 鲍比
You should be proud, Bobby.
就死亡而言 那可一点儿也不寒酸啊
As deaths go, it wasn't too shabby.
振作点啊 同志
Cheer up, mate!
咱一起拯救了这该死的世界
We just saved the sodding world together.
我呢
Me?
一直在庆祝
I've been celebrating.
我一点都不想看见你是怎么庆祝的
I hate to see what you call "Celebrating."
也对 你肯定不待见
Yes, you would.
来一杯吗
Drink?
不用了
No.
让我搞搞清楚
Let me get this straight.
我们刚刚「一起拯救了这该死的世界」
We just "Saved the sodding world together, "
而你竟然不乐意跟我共饮一杯
and you're too good to drink with me?
当然了
Obviously.
而且我怀疑你这儿没我喜欢的牌子
And I doubt that you have my brand.
您想喝什么酒呢 陛下
What's your poison, your highness?
克雷格 至少得是30年陈酿
Craig, aged 30 years, at least.
小学起我就一直喝它
Been drinking it since grade school.
这个嘛
Well…
我只有陈年的劣质威士忌
I got old rotgut…
陈酿六天
Aged six days.
老灌这种酒只会让你的灵魂更加空虚
Swill like that is gonna burn a hole in your soul.
噢 抱歉 我的灵魂才对
Oh, sorry … my soul.
不过这才是你召唤我的真正原因吧
But that's why you called …
有关我们的小交易对吗
our little…deal?
是的 没错
Yeah, well…
是时候履行你的诺言了
It's about time you hold up your end.
把灵魂还给我
and give it back.
还给你
Give it back?
我们说好的
Our deal was…
我们封印路西法 你就把交易停止
we ice Lucifer, you rip up the lease.
你没好好看你的合约
You didn't read your contract.
你他妈的说什么合约呢
The hell you talking about, contract?
第18段的B部分
Paragraph 18, subsection "B, "
印在你私密部位上了
which is on your naughty bits …
我只需要「尽最大努力」
I only have to make "Best efforts"
归还你的灵魂
to give you back your soul.
什么意思
Meaning what?
意思就是
Meaning…
我非常乐意归还
I'd like to…
但却无能为力
but I can't.
你个满嘴跑火车的…
You lying sack of …
十年后
10 years…
你就得下地狱了
You come to daddy.
在那之前 我建议你喝点好东西
Till then, I suggest you start drinking the good stuff.
我就知道你会这么说
I figured you'd say that.
所以在你改变主意之前别想离开这儿
So you can rot here until you change your mind.
- 为什么 因为你低声下气求我吗 - 不
- Why? 'cause you asked nicely? - No.
因为我给你下个了套
'cause I'm going "dateline" on your ass.
我希望这是油漆绘的
I hope that's paint.
没搞错吧
Really?
我该怎么办捏
What am I going to do?
狗狗的气息
Doggy breath.
很清新 对吗
Bracing, isn't it?
现在是你决定的时候了 罗伯特
Ball's in your court, Robert.
是十年的平静生活
10 years of living…
还是当十年的狗粮
or 10 years as alpo.
这事儿没完
This ain't over.
我是绝对不会改变主意的
I wouldn't have it any other way.
祝猎魔快乐
Happy hunting.
[邪恶力量 第6季第4集]
（基诺沙县 威斯康辛州 如今）
没有电磁反应
No EMF.
尸体有什么线索吗
Find anything in there?
是的 我找到了个爪子
Yeah, I got some kind of claw.
这是什么东西的爪子啊
What in the hell has a claw like that?
问得好
That is a good question.
他说不定上厕所呢
Maybe he's in the can.
什么事
Yeah?
- 咋了 你摔地上爬不起来了么 - 不好笑
- What happened, you fall and can't get up? - Hilarious.
- 有屁快放 - 我们在威斯康辛州
- What's up? - We're in Wisconsin.
六具尸体 胸腔被挖开
Six bodies, chests cracked wide open.
没有电磁反应 没有硫磺也没有巫术袋
No EMF, no sulfur, no hex bags.
我们还发现了这个 等等
We did find this, though. Hang on.
好了 看你的电脑
All right, check your wang.
这倒是没见过
That's a new one.
你尽快查清楚这是啥东西的爪子
Yeah, we need an I.D. Asap.
这东西可到处撒野呢
This thing's on a rampage.
你有线索了就打给我
Call as soon as you dig something up.
迪恩 我有点忙
Dean, I'm a little busy.
赶快从你的软香温玉里起来吧
Well, then kick bo derek out of your bathtub.
我们在办正事呢
We got a case here.
等我电话吧
I'll call you back.
操蛋
Balls.
（苏福尔斯大学图书馆）
快点发动啊
Come on.
搞毛啊
操蛋
Balls.
你们遇见的是女妖
You are hunting a lamia.
啥
Come again?
是一种怪物
It's a monster.
吃人心 喝人血
Juices hearts, chugs the blood.
还没听说过这东西出现在希腊之外的地方
Never heard of one popping up outside of Greece, though.
这怪物貌似移民了
Yeah, well, looks like this freak has immigrated.
跑来威斯康星州吃人
It's snacking on cheese-heads.
有何对策
How do we gank it?
有很多方法
There's a couple of ways.
最方便的是被神父开过光的银制刀具
Easiest is a silver knife blessed by a padre.
知道了
Gotcha.
兔崽子 不用谢了
You're welcome.
我还在这儿呢
Hey! I'm still here!
好啊 暴脾气大叔
Hey, there, cranky.
你去那么久 我还以为你酒精中毒昏倒了呢
You were gone so long, I just assumed alcoholic coma.
- 我们说到哪里了 - 你的灵魂
- Where were we? - Your soul.
对
Right.
说吧
Talk.
瞧瞧你 手忙脚乱
Look at you … all in a rush.
有前戏
Foreplay…
才有高潮嘛
gets you more play.
把克劳力的名字告诉我
I want Crowley's name …
他真正的名字
his real name,
他还是人类时候的名字
back when he was flesh and blood.
把恶魔绑在你的地下室里
Does tying demons up in your basement make you feel better.
是不是能减轻你杀害妻子的罪恶感
about that time you killed your wife?
那是什么
What's that?
不认识吗 是你的东西呢
You don't recognize them? They're yours.
没用的
It won't work.
只是个传说而已
It's a myth.
那你就无须多虑了
Then you got nothing to worry about.
我不能说
I can't!
你无法想象他会怎样对我
You don't know what he'll do to me.
- 现在你面临的是我 - 你不明白
- Right now, you better worry about me. - You don't get it.
他是王
He's the king.
十字路口之王 这我知道
King of the crossroads … I've heard the speech.
不
No.
地狱之王
King of hell.
你还不去开门吗
You gonna get that or what?
马西
Marcy.
- 鲍比·辛格 我们做邻居多久了 - 六个月
- Bobby Singer, how long have we been neighbors? - Six months.
你现在是不是应该
Well, don't you think it's time.
欢迎我成为你的邻居了
you welcomed me to the neighborhood?
我最拿手的生姜蜜桃馅饼
My famous ginger-peach cobbler.
闻一下 我可是个天才厨师
Take a whiff. Seriously, I'm a genius.
救命啊 来人啊
Help me! Somebody help me!
那是
It's, um…
无聊的恐怖电影
stupid horror flicks.
我有恐怖片情结
Guilty pleasure.
我超爱恐怖电影
I love scary movies.
你看《堕入地狱》没有
Hey, have you seen "Drag me to hell"?
能免则免吧
Trying to avoid it.
但是真的很赞
But it's fantastic.
星期六 七点 来我家
Saturday, 7:00, my house.
我给你做晚饭
I'll fix you dinner,
我会做一些拿手的白巧克力爆米花
and I'll whip up a batch of my famous white-chocolate popcorn,
我们边吃边看
and we'll watch it.
行吗
Deal?
听起来不错 马西 但是
That sounds super, Marcy, but, uh…
好的 没事
Okay, no worries.
还有一件事
Um, hey, one other thing …
我的碎木机 真是一坨废铁
Uh, my wood chipper … it's a piece of crap.
不知道怎么就坏了
You know, it just broke down on me,
我听说你挺能干的
and … and I hear that you're quite handy.
你能不能过来 帮我看看
Maybe you could come over and…take a look …
随便什么时候都可以
You know, just whenever.
好的 我尽力而为吧
Yeah, I'll see what I can do.
好的
Okay.
那好
回见
Okay, see you soon.
听上去人不错哦
Aw! She sounds nice.
鲍比 你要先和她大干一场
Are you gonna make sweet love to her.
再把她杀死吗
before you stab her to death, Bobby?
你通常不都这么干么
That is your usual thing, right?
告诉我克劳力的真名
I want Crowley's name now!
- 克劳力的真名 - 我说
- Crowley's name! - Okay!
我说
Okay.
麦克劳德
Macleod.
费格斯·麦克劳德 我发誓是真名
Fergus Macleod. I swear.
我们在背后叫他幸运妖精
We call him Lucky The Leprechaun behind his back.
麦克劳德是苏格兰名字 天才
Macleod's Scottish, Einstein.
你得偿所愿了 现在送我回去
You got what you want. Now send me back …
不
No.
我们说好的
We had a deal!
我心有余而力不足
Gave it my best effort.
不
No!
加思 有啥情况
Yeah, Garth, what do you got?
我从未听说过吸血鬼会那样做
I've never heard of a vamp doing that.
那应该不关我们的事
Doesn't sound like our kind of thing.
最好把这事儿告诉联邦调查局
Better drop a dime to the FBI.
威利斯 联邦调查局
Willis. FBI.
不 加思 不是打给我
No, Garth, not me,
是打给真正的联邦调查局
the FBI. The real FBI.
你怎么活到现在的
How are you still alive?
我是坎索尔
You got Castle.
请说
Yeah.
我是威利斯
Yeah. Willis.
她当然是我们的人
Uh-huh. Of course she's one of ours.
如果她想要去挖那个坟
And if she says she's got to dig that grave up,
你最好答应
you better damn well let her.
太好了 你在家
Oh, good, you're home.
听着 你得帮我埋个尸体
Listen, you got to help me bury a body.
你干嘛把它带到这里来
Why'd you bring it here?
条子们抓我呢
The law is on my tail.
不然你以为呢
What was your guess?
干嘛 他们走运而已
What? What? What? They got lucky.
是啊 要不就是你身手变慢了
Yeah, or you're getting slow.
我身手变慢
I'm getting slow.
这话还是从“全职接线员”嘴里说出来的
Yeah, says Mr."Sits on his ass all day taking calls."
吸血鬼 变形怪 还是什么
Vamp? Shifter? What?
都不是
None of the above.
狼神吗
Okami?
你在哪里解决它的
Where'd you shiv it?
听好啊 比林斯（位于蒙大拿州）
Get this … Billings.
我唯一一次遇见狼神还是在日本
Only time I ever saw one of these was in Japan.
没有人在日本以外看到过他们
Duh … no one's ever seen one of these except in Japan.
顺便一提
For what it's worth,
萨姆和迪恩在威斯康星州追踪一个女妖
Sam and Dean are tracking a Lamia in Wisconsin.
不会吧 他们不是只在希腊活动么
Get out. I thought they never leave Greece.
怪物最近都
Monsters lately …
是我多想了 还是本来就很奇怪
is it me, or is it weird?
这次肯定出事了
Yeah, well, it's… definitely something.
你有铲子吗
So, you got a shovel?
我光明节的礼物就要这个了
Man! I know what I want for hanukkah.
所以说 那混蛋叫费格斯·麦克劳德
So, the son of a bitch's name is Fergus Macleod?
对 这就是他的名字
That's the son of a bitch's name.
你要从哪儿找起
Where you gonna look?
苏格兰
Scotland.
克劳力无意中提到他喜欢喝克雷格酒
Crowley let slip that he likes Craig.
是一种
It's, um…
苏格兰威士忌
It's Scotch.
只在凯思内斯郡最北部的
Only made and sold in a tiny area.
小部分地区酝酿以及销售
on the north tip of Caithness county.
酒丝浓郁 辣劲十足
It's peaty and sharp.
余味是柑橘和烟草的味道
with a long finish of citrus and tobacco notes.
怎么了 我难道是一个粗人吗
Hey, what? What am I, a heathen?
我知道克雷格这种酒
I know what Craig is.
我有预感
Well, I got a hunch that.
当克劳力还是人类的时候
that's where Crowley lived and died,
他就是在那里度过一生的
back when he was a human …
在他从地狱里浴火重生成为恶魔的
A few hundred years before he got the big squeeze in hell.
几百年之前吧
and came out a demon.
我在那边有熟人
You know, I got contacts over there.
我可以打几个电话问问
I can make a few calls.
我没要你帮我
I ain't asking for no help.
我不必尊求你的意见
I'm not asking you your permission.
喂
Yeah.
还有什么办法可以杀了女妖
What's another way to kill a lamia?
那把神父祝福过的银刀不管用吗
Well, what happened to the silver knife blessed by a priest?
没什么用
That didn't pan out.
你有后备计划吗
What's plan "B"?
警察
Police!
- 操蛋 - 拜托 鲍比 快点说
- Balls! - Come on, Bobby. Get the lead out.
- 你在哪儿 - 教堂 教区长的家里
- Where are you? - The church … in a rectory.
- 有厨房吗 - 有
- Is there a kitchen? - Yeah.
找到盐和迷迭香
Find salt and rosemary.
快开门 辛格
Open up, Singer!
辛格先生 我是亚当斯探员
Mr. Singer, I'm Agent Adams.
我相信你肯定认识米尔斯警长
I believe you know Sheriff Mills.
等等 我跟我妈打电话呢
My mom. Just a second.
- 迷迭香我找到了 - 很好
- Rosemary! I got it! - Great, great.
把它和盐搅拌 高温加热
Now blend the herbs, sauté over a high heat.
仔细烧
Cook well.
小萨姆 要点火啦
Sammy! Fire in the hole!
好 很好
Okay, great, great.
慢慢享用烤肉吧 妈妈
Enjoy the roast, mom.
你见过这个男人吗
Have you seen this man?
鲁弗斯·特纳 又称卢瑟·范德罗斯
Rufus Turner, AKA Luther Vandross,
又称鲁本·斯达德
Aka Ruben Studdard?
没 没见过这个傻叉
No. Never seen that dick.
你怎么知道他是个傻叉
How you know he's a dick?
我猜的
Lucky guess.
有意思了
Funny.
我几个在公路上工作的朋友告诉我
Cause I got a couple guys working the highway,
他们看见他到你这儿来了 还带了一具尸体
said they saw him pull in here, carrying a body.
这不可能
Well, that's ridiculous.
今天是工作日 我得去…
Look, it's a work day. I got to …
我们只想搜查下你的屋子
We just want to take a look around.
你有搜查令吗 小子
You got a warrant, sonny?
我想我用不着 先生
Well, do I need one…Sir?
好了伙计们 别整官僚这套 都少说两句
Okay, fellas, put the rulers away. Zip up.
听着 鲍比他确实是个…
Look, Bobby here's kind of a…
急脾气
crank.
他也绝对不是个政府拥护者
And he ain't what you call a fan of big brother.
但我和他
But me and him …
我逮捕你有几年了 十年吗
How long I been arresting you now, 10 years?
差不多吧
Thereabouts.
我们有点交情
Yeah, we got a history.
你说让我来搜查他的屋子怎么样
So, what do you say you just let me scope the place out?
可以吗 你可以在外面等
That okay? You can just wait outside.
就五分钟
Five minutes.
太好了
Great.
你干嘛把他赶到外面去
Why'd you send him outside?
因为我不觉得你想把他留在这儿
'cause I didn't think you'd want him in here.
确实 我地下室里有具尸体
I don't. I've got a body in the basement.
这不结了
My point.
但我在后院里还埋了一具
Yeah, but I've got another body buried in the yard.
该死的
Damn it.
他走了
He's not there.
操蛋
Balls.
辛格先生 请过来一下
Mr. Singer, come with me please.
你介意解释一下这个吗
You mind explaining this?
咋的了 化粪池爆炸不行吗
What, you never had a septic tank explode on you?
我已经好好清理过了
I got it pretty well cleaned up,
但你还是注意下你脚下
but watch where you step.
快给我回来
Get back here.
回个毛 我都开了两个州了 鲍比
Get back … I'm two states over, Bobby.
我回不去
I can't …
那个狼神没有死
The okami ain't dead.
它当然死了
Of course it is.
- 你用竹制匕首了吗 - 用了
- Did you use a bamboo dagger? - Yeah.
是被神道牧师祝福过的吗
Blessed by a shinto priest?
我又不是弱智 鲍比
I'm not an imbecile, bobby.
你刺了七次吗
Did you stab it seven times?
是五次
Five times.
应该是七次
It's seven.
不 我很确定是五次
No, I'm pretty sure it's five.
很明显 是七次
Well, clearly it's seven times.
那个挖的洞空了
The damn hole is empty.
你找到它的时候它在袭击什么
What was it feeding on when you found it?
单身的白人女性
Single, white females…
趁她们睡觉的时候
while they slept.
鲍比
Bobby?
你的房间在哪里
Where's your bedroom?
鲍比 我尽量不抓狂
Bobby, I am trying to keep my cool here.
你拿着散弹枪在我家干嘛
What are you doing in my house with a shotgun?
你看没看见啥奇怪的东西
Have you see anything… Weird?
除你之外吗
You mean besides you?
鲍比 不
Bobby! No!
小心啊
Look out!
我…
I, uh…
你家切碎机不是坏了吗
I thought your chipper was broke.
我就这么一说 好让你过来
I just said that to get you over here.
这样啊
Oh.
那…
Well…
我想我倒是能来吃个饭啥的
I guess I could come over for dinner some night.
会蛮有趣的吧
Might be fun.
我看还是算了
I don't think so.
我的生活一直这样
Story of my life.
还喘气呐
You're still alive, huh?
别这么大惊小怪的
Don't act so surprised.
- 那女魔头怎么样了 - 干掉了
- How about godzilla? - Put her down.
你不会刚好手边放着
So, you just happened to have a bamboo dagger.
一把开了光的竹制匕首吧
blessed by a shinto priest laying around?
是切碎机
Wood chipper.
这样子啊 切碎机
Oh, okeydokey. Wood chipper.
有这东西 估计啥都顶了
That … that pretty much trumps…Everything.
听着 鲍比
Listen, uh, Bobby, um…
谢谢你
Thank you.
是我搞砸了
I screwed up.
算了吧
Forget it.
计较起来 我欠你的比你欠我的多多了
I figure I still owe you more than you owe me.
那好吧 你现在又要多欠我个人情
All righty. Then add one more thing to the list.
我有克劳力的消息了
I got a lead on your boy Crowley …
又称费格斯·罗利克·麦克劳德
Aka Fergus Rodric Macleod,
祖籍苏格兰凯思内斯 1661年生
Born in Canisbay, Scotland … 1661.
好极了 这能有啥用
Great. I don't know what that's gonna get me.
好吧 下面这个 老鲍
All right, well, then, behind door number two, Bob…
克劳力有个儿子
Crowley had a son.
有意思了
Did he, now?
没错 他叫加文
Yeah, name of Gavin.
他父母过世后便往来于大西洋
Moved across the pond after his parents bit it.
指挥一艘商船
and captained a trading ship.
1723年在马萨诸塞州死后下了地狱
That went down in Massachusetts in 1723.
约三十年前 一帮疯狂的海洋学家找到了残骸
A couple of Cousteau wannabes found the wreck about 30 years ago.
- 他们找到了他的尸骨吗 - 没
- They fish out his bones? - No, no.
但找到了他的图章戒指
They did find his signet ring, though.
现作为「深海宝藏」系列展的一部分
It's part of the "Treasures from the deep" Exhibit.
在安多弗德海洋博物馆展出
At the Maritime Museum in Andover.
我要那枚戒指
I need that ring.
哎呦喂
Ooh!
你这是在求我吗 老鲍
Oh, are you, um … you asking for my help, bob?
鲍比
Bobby?
我不过是要枚戒指
I'm asking for a ring.
你要能帮忙
And…I'd appreciate your…
我会很领情的
help getting it.
早替你想好了 哥们
I'm way ahead of you, brother.
我这就去安多弗
I'm headed for Andover now.
大概午夜就到了
I should be there around midnight.
你那个…
You're, um…
你是打算交换人质 是吗
You're thinking hostage exchange, aren't you?
拿到戒指后召唤他儿子的鬼魂
I mean, get the ring, you can summon junior's ghost.
捉到鬼魂 和克劳力换回你的灵魂
Get the ghost, you can swap Crowley his son for your soul.
差不多这意思吧
Something like that.
但愿能成功吧
Let's hope that works out.
迪恩 你还好吧
Dean, you all right?
还好 那女妖的事挺顺利
Yeah. Yeah, the Lamia grilled up fine.
我听着话音儿不对啊
I sense a "But" coming on.
是萨姆 鲍比
It's Sam, Bobby.
我就是感觉他变了
He's just … he's different.
我也知道
You know, and I get it.
有过那样的经历
You go through something like that,
人是会变
And … and you change.
但是
But…
我就是觉得不对劲
Something's not right to me.
- 迪恩 - 那一年里好多事我都想不通
- Dean … I've got a few questions about that year …
你一直在他身边 而我没有
When you saw him and I didn't.
迪恩 我又来一电话
Dean, I got another call.
- 啥 - 稍等
- You what? - Just hang on.
这电话我得接 很重要
I got to take this. It's important.
啥事比萨姆还重要
More important than Sam?
鲍比
Bobby?
鲁弗斯
Rufus?
鲍比 好消息是我拿到戒指了 但是
The good news is I snagged the ring, Bobby. However …
- 不是吧 - 没错
- Tell me that ain't - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
给你猜三下谁在追我 先把医务人员排除吧
Three guesses, and one of 'em … it ain't the paramedics.
听我说鲍比 我得找个地方藏这戒指
Listen, Bobby, I-I got to stash this ring.
可别吞下去
But don't swallow it.
行吧 鲍比 这就吞
Right. I'm swallowing it, Bobby.
我说别吞
Don't swallow it.
该死
Damn it.
我去
Aw, hell!
下来 从车上下来
Get on the ground! Out of the car!
我有权利的 妈的
I know my rights, damn it!
迪恩 还在吗
You still there, Dean?
鲍比 你搞什么
Bobby, what the hell?
对不起
I-I'm sorry.
你知道的 这些事
You know, you are the one person.
我只能跟你一个人说
that I can talk to about this stuff …
萨姆的事 还有丢下莉莎和本
About … about Sam, about leaving Lisa and Ben.
我想说 我现在都不知道该怎么做
I mean, I don't … I don't even know which way is up right now.
鲍比
Bobby?
在吗
Hello?
我听着呢 孩子 只是现在不是时候
I-I hear you, son. I-it just ain't a good time.
好 那个啥
Yeah, okay. You know what?
当我没说
Forget it.
我在这儿跟他妈个姑娘似的吐槽
I mean, I'm baring my soul like a freaking girl here,
你也有自己的事要做
And, uh … and you've got stuff to do.
那个 没关系的
Well, that is … that's fine.
没事儿 不过说真的 你这样挺自私的
That's fine, but seriously, though … a little selfish.
不是什么都得围着你转
Not all about you.
你弟弟呢
Where's your brother?
外边呢
Outside.
叫进来
Get him.
开着扬声器呢 鲍比
You're on speaker, Bobby.
萨姆 迪恩
Sam? Dean?
我爱你们 视如己出
I love you like my own. I do.
但有时候
But sometimes…
有时候
…Sometimes,
你俩真是我见过
You two are the whiniest,
最爱发牢骚 最自我中心的混球
most self-absorbed sons of bitches I ever met.
你们说我自私
I'm selfish?
我哪里自私了
Me?
我为你们付出了一切 所有的一切
I do everything for you … everything!
你们要我查传说资料
You need some lore scrounged up?
你们要我来救你们的小命
You need your asses pulled out of the fire?
就连你们闹别扭我还得听你们诉苦
You need someone to bitch to about each other?
你们啥都找我帮忙 而我
You call me, and I come through …
我哪次他妈的不是赴汤蹈火
Every…Damn…Time.
结果到头来呢
And what do I get for it?
我他妈连个屁都没有
Jack with a side of squat!
- 鲍比 - 老子话还没说完
- Bobby - Do I sound like I'm done?
给我听着 我知道你们有了麻烦
Now, look, I know you've got issues.
天知道我怎么知道的
God knows I know.
但我要告诉你们一点
But I got a news flash for you.
地球不是绕着你们转的
You ain't the center of the universe.
现在 你们有没有想起来
Now, it may have slipped your mind.
我的灵魂在克劳力手里
That Crowley owns my soul.
时间每分每秒在流逝
And the meter is running!
如果我就这么干等着 就死定了
And I will be damned if I am gonna sit around.
我得下地狱了
And … and be damned!
你们俩能不能别再给我唧唧歪歪
So, how about you two sack up.
就帮我这么一次 行不行
And help me for once?!
鲍比 你尽管开口
Bobby, all … all you got to do is ask.
不管要我们帮什么忙都行
Anything you need, we're there.
我收到了马西·沃德的电话
Got a call from Marcy Ward.
听起来她好像遭遇了一次入侵民宅
Seems she had a little home invasion.
我告诉她说我会查 不用记录在档了
Told her I'd look into it. Didn't bother filing a report.
多谢
Thanks.
我要你帮个忙
Need a favor.
卢瑟·范德罗斯来了么
Luther Vandross turn up?
转告一下我的仰慕之情哈
Tell him I'm a fan.
他的真名是鲁弗斯·特纳
His real name's Rufus Turner.
他因盗窃罪被关在麻省的安多弗
He's being held in Andover, Mass., on a burglary charge.
我想让你把他引渡到这来
Need you to get him extradited here.
什么罪名
Extradited for what?
谋杀罪
Murder.
你还真没说笑
You're not joking.
你知道引渡一名罪犯需要什么吗
Do you have any idea what it takes to extradite a prisoner?
需要得到庭谕和地检官许可
I'd need a court order, permission from the D.A.
我得向各种人员进行申请
I-I would have to call in every marker I got.
还得处理各种手续
and hand out a few to boot.
这么说还是有希望的
So, you're saying there's a chance.
就算老天保佑我们成功了 然后呢
And if by some miracle we can get him here, then what?
你那伙计在这里面临谋杀指控
Then your pal's here on a murder charge.
你准备怎么把他救出去
How you gonna to get him out from under that one?
这让我来担心好了
Let me handle the "B" Side.
我喜欢你 鲍比
I like you, bobby.
可这会让我丢了饭碗
But this could nuke my career.
我为这个镇子付出了很多
Look, I've done a lot for this town …
只会比你知道得更多
Some you know about, some you don't.
我真的不擅长求人
And I'm not real good at this whole "Asking for help" Thing,
但是…
But…
抱歉 我做不到
I'm sorry, Bobby. I can't.
想我了吗
Miss me?
- 你怎么 - 别问
- How did you… - Don't ask.
给你一小时 之后我再报告联调局
You got one hour, and then I call the feds.
这家伙跑了
And tell them he busted out.
多谢
Thanks.
要是我丢了工作 老娘跟你没完
I lose my job over this, I am taking it out of your ass.
戒指还在你胃里吧
Tell me the ring is still in your stomach.
我去煮点沸水
I'll go boil some water.
干嘛
What?
[咒语]
加文·麦克劳德吗
Gavin Macleod?
这里…
is…
这里是地狱吗
Is this hell?
那得看你的表现了
That's gonna depend on you.
你是费格斯·麦克劳德的儿子吗
Are you Fergus Macleod's boy?
你和我
You and me…
坐下来好好聊聊吧
Are gonna have a nice, long chat.
靠 你看起来真萎靡呀
Well, you look like hammered crap.
你还是这么会挑时候
And you're a vision, as always.
老是这一套 有完没完呐
Don't we both know how this game ends?
说真的 鲍比
Really, bobby…
你真该消停一下了
You got to know when to fold 'em.
我听说
Word on the street.
自从路西法又被封印以来
is that ever since Lucifer went to the pokey,
你就是地狱的老大了
You're the big kahuna downstairs.
- 看来你读过交易内容了 - 和天堂有麻烦了吗
- I see you've been reading the trades. - Trouble in paradise?
哥们 你想也想不到的麻烦
Mate, you have no idea.
我本以为…
I thought…
一旦我掌了权
that when I got the corner office …
我以为…
I thought it was all gonna be…
地狱就会变得皆大欢喜
rainbows and 2-headed puppies.
但说实话
but if I'm being honest…
感觉结果还是一团糟
It's been hell.
这也不奇怪
Thought that was the point.
你知道恶魔的毛病是啥么
You know what the problem with demons is?
- 他们本性难移 - 一点没错
- They're demons? - Exactly.
一帮邪恶又背信弃义的废物
Evil, lying prats, the whole lot of them.
又蠢又笨
And stupid.
我本想另指一条路给他们 更好的路
Try to show them a-a new way … a better way …
结果我得到什么
And what do you get?
屁都没有
Bugger all!
要知道 曾几何时
You know, there's days that I think.
我还觉得路西法的「把所有人都变成恶魔」
Lucifer's whole "Spike anything with black eyes" Plan.
那计划不错呢
wasn't half bad.
一吐为快的感觉真好
Feels good to get that off my chest.
我们该多来几次
We should make this a thing.
我看起来像是心理医生吗
Do I look like Dr. Phil to you?
有点像
A little.
好吧
Anyhoo…
你肯定不是叫我来做客的
Obviously not here for a social call,
有何贵干
So on with it.
我想…
I want …
你就不用重复了
I'll save you the recap.
事实上 不如让我帮你概括下
In fact, I'll do the shorthand for you.
你说 我想要回我的灵魂 混球
I want my soul back, idjit!
我说 不行
afraid not.
你说 别逼老子来硬的
but I'm surly, and I got a beard!
快还给我
Gimme!
诸如此类
blah, blah, blah,
和你这样的乡巴佬说话
Homespun cornpone insult,
真是侮辱了我的聪敏才智啊
witty retort from yours truly.
归根结蒂就是 你什么也得不到
The bottom line is… You get bubkes.
说完了吧
Are we done?
才刚开始呢
Just getting started.
加文
Gavin?
是你吗
Is that you?
真是… 好久不见了
I-it's … it's been so long.
我好爱你…
I love you so …
不好意思
Sorry.
用你的灵魂换我儿子吗
Your soul for my boy … that's it, right?
不得不称赞你
I got to give you credit.
这件事你想得真妙啊
for thinking outside the box on that one,
但问题是 我讨厌这小杂种
But problem is, I loathe the little bastard.
你想折磨他吗
You want to torture him?
让我一边坐着好好欣赏吧
Just let me pull up a chair, and I'll watch.
烧了他的尸骨 把他送来地狱
Hell, burn his bones, send him down to me.
我们就可以一家团聚了
We can have a family reunion.
没错吧 儿子
That's right, son?
你可是选错了交易筹码 朋友
You picked the wrong bargaining chip this time, my friend.
他才不是筹码
He ain't a chip.
我只是利用他 挖掘一下你的过去
I was just using him to dig up dirt on you.
因为加文讨厌你
And since Gavin hates you.
你是讨厌他 而他甚至更加讨厌你
Maybe even more than you hate him,
能够一吐为快 他可是乐意至极啊
He was more than happy to squawk.
你告诉他什么了 儿子
What did you tell him, son?
所有的一切
Everything.
现在我全都知道了
I know it all now…
费格斯
Fergus.
你可能现在是威风的地狱之主
Now, you may be king of the dirtbags here,
但生前 你不过是个微不足道的裁缝
But in life, you were nothing but a two-bit tailor.
为了五斗米而折腰
Who sold his soul.
出卖了自己的灵魂
In exchange for an extra 3 inches below the belt.
人不为己天诛地灭
Just trying to hit double digits.
这么说
So…
你是挖到了一些我的过去
You got a glimpse behind the curtain.
那又怎样
And?
现在
And…
我知道你被葬在哪儿了
Now I know where you're planted.
好啊 克劳力
Hiya, Crowley.
迪恩
Dean.
好久不见丫
It's been a long time.
- 啥时聚聚呗 - 当然
- We should get together. - Sure.
我们回来就能聚了
We'll have to do that when I get back.
回来是啥意思
Back?
是这样
Yeah.
我和萨姆 我们在国外
Me and Sam … we've gone international.
事实上 我们在你的老巢
In fact, we're in your neck of the woods.
你过去真的穿裙子的吗
Did you really used to wear a skirt?
是苏格兰男用短裙
A kilt.
我有很健壮的小腿
I had very athletic calves.
- 你们在搞什么鬼 - 玩骨牌呗
- What's the game? - Dominoes.
其实 我们刚把你的骨头挖出来
In fact, we just dug yours up.
荒唐透顶
This is ridiculous.
烧骨头这种方法 不过是个传说
The whole burning-bones thing … I-it's a myth.
你的手下可不这么认为
I know an employee of yours who'd disagree.
那是什么
What's that?
没认出来吗 那是你的东西
You don't recognize 'em? They're yours.
原来她是这么死的
That's where she got to.
你们这些恶魔
You demons.
总是自以为非比寻常
You think you're something special,
但事实上 你们只是灵魂
But you're just spirits …
扭曲 堕落 邪恶的灵魂
Twisted, perverted, evil spirits,
但归根结蒂
But end of the day,
你们不过是些自负的鬼魂
You're nothing but ghosts with an ego.
我们只要点燃遗骨
We torch your bones,
你就会灰飞烟灭
You go up in flames.
听到了吗 克劳力
You hear that, Crowley?
我在为你点打火机呢
That's me flicking my bic for you.
你的遗骨交换我的灵魂
Your bones for my soul.
一次
Going once.
两次
Going twice.
我去
Bollocks!
对于我的腿你就不必做什么改动了吧
You can go ahead and leave in the part about my legs.
很高兴与你做交易
Pleasure doing business with you.
现在 要是你不介意的话…
Now, if you don't mind…
这是我的遗骨
I believe those are mine.
知道我现在怎么想不
You know, now that I think about it,
我干嘛不直接
Maybe I'll just…
烧了它们呢
…Napalm your ass anyhow.
迪恩
Dean…
他是个混蛋
He's a dick…
但交易要讲信用
But a deal's a deal.
我不用你帮我说话 大高个
I don't need you to fight my battles for me, moose.
滚开
Get bent.
现在我得失陪一下了
Now, if you'll excuse me…
我还有一地狱的恶魔要管
I have a little hell to raise.
多谢你俩小子助我一臂之力
I appreciate you boys lend a hand.
能这么整下克劳力那娘炮要我们怎的都行
Hey, anytime we get to punk Crowley works for us.
是啊
Yeah.
我知道你有多么「喜欢」坐飞机
Still, knowing how much you love flying the friendly skies,
九小时的飞行可不是盖的
I guess a 9-hour plane trip was no picnic.
你怎么熬过来的 把自己灌醉吗
What'd you do, drink your way through it?
我没事
I was fine.
才不 一路上他吓得吐了四袋子了
No, he white-knuckled his way through four puke bags.
至少我很清醒
Well, at least I was sober.
如果有混蛋想轻举妄动 想也别想
Some nutjob decided to try something, I was ready.
我捏着叉子呢
I had a fork.
听着
Listen, um…
我早先说过的话…
About the things I said earlier…
我当时心情很差
I was in a tough spot,
- 我想我是… - 你说得没错 鲍比
- and I-I guess I was … - you were right, Bobby.
我们太想当然了
We take you for granted.
多年来 都是你为我们收拾烂摊子 鲍比
You've been cleaning up our messes for years, Bobby.
要是没有你 我都不敢想象
Without you, I don't even want.
我和萨姆会是怎么个死法
to think about where me and Sam would have ended up.
好吧 这么肉麻的话还是少说点
Okay, then. Let's roll credits on this chick flick.
旅途愉快
You boys have a safe flight.
吃点儿当地美食
And, uh, try some of the local grub.
我听说很有异域风情
I hear it's…Exotic.
必须去
Oh, yeah, no, definitely, we are.
听说这儿有奥利弗花园餐厅
I hear they have an Olive Garden.
我是威利斯
Willis.
是 还是我们这的精英探员呢
Yeah, he is. One of our best agents, in fact.